<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Smart Finance Guide — Insurance, Loans &amp; AI Tools</title><link>https://smartfinance.guide/pages/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Smart Finance Guide — Insurance, Loans &amp; AI Tools</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://smartfinance.guide/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Smart Finance Guide</title><link>https://smartfinance.guide/pages/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smartfinance.guide/pages/about/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="our-mission">Our Mission&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Smart Finance Guide helps millions of Americans make smarter financial decisions. We provide free, expert-reviewed guides on insurance, personal finance, loans, and technology tools.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="editorial-standards">Editorial Standards&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Every article on Smart Finance Guide follows strict editorial standards:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Accuracy First.&lt;/strong> All financial data, rates, and statistics are verified against primary sources including official company rate pages, government databases, and industry reports. We update our content monthly to ensure accuracy.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Expert Review.&lt;/strong> Our content is reviewed by licensed insurance agents, certified financial planners (CFP), and industry professionals before publication.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://smartfinance.guide/pages/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://smartfinance.guide/pages/privacy-policy/</guid><description>&lt;p>&lt;em>Last updated: February 2026&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="information-we-collect">Information We Collect&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Smart Finance Guide collects limited information to improve your experience:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Automatically Collected:&lt;/strong> We use Google Analytics to collect anonymous usage data including pages visited, time spent, browser type, and device information. This data is aggregated and cannot identify individual users.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Voluntarily Provided:&lt;/strong> If you subscribe to our newsletter, we collect your email address. We never sell or share email addresses with third parties.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>